nissan.in 2018-12-28

# Privacy Policy | Nissan India

* * *

##  Privacy

We value your privacy.

NISSAN MOTOR INDIA PRIVATE LIMITED (NMIPL) collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. NMIPL is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell or rent this information to others. We will only share this information with our affiliates and dealers, and marketing partners contracted to do business on our behalf (e.g., brochure fulfillment). NMIPL uses two types of user information: anonymous information gathered from cookies and log files, and personal information you provide us for certain services. See below for definitions of each of these methods.

* * *

##  Anonymous Information - Cookies and Log Files

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to personal information, until a user provides that information (see below). If a user rejects or deletes the cookie, he/she may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. For example, the user will not be able to receive notification of special offers, or participate in any contests that may take place. Cookies also enable us to track and aggregate clickstream behavior data. By doing this we can better target the interests of our users and enhance their experience on our site. Nissan also maintains standard web logs that record data about all visitors to this Web site. These logs may contain: The Internet domain from which you access this site. Your IP address (Your computer is automatically assigned an IP address when you surf the Internet. Your IP address is either static or dynamic. A static IP address may be identifiable to you; a dynamic address is usually not identifiable to you). The type of browser and operating system you use. The date and time you visited this site. The pages you viewed on this site. The address of the Web site from which you linked. Nissan uses web log and clickstream information to help us design our site, to identify popular site features and to make the site more useful for visitors. Web logs are recorded in sequential files, and we normally do not attempt to identify individuals from these logs. However, we may use web logs to identify persons attempting to break into, disrupt, or damage our Site. We may share web log information with law enforcement personnel if we believe evidence exists, or is likely to occur, of a violation of federal, state or local laws or regulations. Nissan advertising at other non-Nissan sites may be serviced by Nissan service providers, who may use cookies to collect information about your visits to those sites. Information collected may include the pages visited, date and time, browser information and/or IP address. We normally make no attempt to link this information to you personally, except under circumstances described above. This information is gathered in order to help us customize and target our advertising to the needs and interests of our customers. If you wish to opt out of this tracking at our advertising at third party sites, please visit the site of our service provider, NMIPL. Should you decide that you do not wish to participate in NMIPL -enabled information delivery, you can opt out from there, or by clicking here. 

* * *

##  Volunteering Personal Information

Users may choose to volunteer personal information (name, e-mail address, phone number, etc.) in order for us to provide them with services such as brochure and information requests, surveys and contests, site announcements, and special offers at the time of the request or in the future. If you previously gave us your e-mail address and no longer wish to receive e-mail announcements, you can have your name removed from our e-mail list by sending an e-mail, calling, or by sending regular mail. Nissan does not sell or rent user information to any third parties. We share user information with our affiliates and dealers, and marketing partners contracted to do business on our behalf (e.g., brochure fulfillment). When the user signs up for certain services and offers on our site, we will share names, or other contact information necessary for any associate third party to provide these services. Nissan will share user information in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is collected. If a user’s personal information changes, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct or update that user’s personal data provided to us. This can be done by contacting Nissan Consumer Affairs 

* * *

##  Security

Nissan takes all reasonable precautions to protect our users’ information, both while the information is being transmitted and after it is received by us. When our credit pre-approval form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL 128-bit encryption software, an industry standard for reputable organizations. While on a secure page, such as our credit pre-approval application form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to unlocked, or open, when you are just "surfing." Furthermore, once the information has been received by us, we use security procedures and policies commensurate with industry standards to safeguard against loss, theft, unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification and disclosure. If you have any questions about the security of our Web site, you can send an e-mail to NMIPL. 

* * *

##  Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that NMIPL is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each Web site that collects personal information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

* * *

##  Notification of Changes

We retain the right to change this privacy policy at any time. We will display those changes to this page so that users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will use, share, and disclose all information in accordance with the privacy policy in effect at the time the information was collected.

* * *

##  Certain Disclosures

Nissan may disclose any data, whether personally identifiable or not, to any person performing audit, legal, operational or other similar services for Nissan. Whenever possible, we will require any recipient of personal information for these purposes to agree in writing to hold the information in confidence, to use the information only for the permitted purpose, and to return or destroy the information when the services are completed. We may also disclose any data, whether personally identifiable or not, when required to do so by subpoena, court order, or warrant. Whenever feasible, Nissan will notify the effected user by e-mail that such disclosure will or has occurred. We may also disclose any data, whether personally identifiable or not, when we reasonably deem it necessary to protect the safety of (i) an individual, (ii) the public, or (iii) the security and reliability of Nissan and/or this Web site.
